Izumi-san, how are you feeling?
My sunburn hurts...
Well, it was quite sunny at the river.
Yeah... Maybe I cut a little too loose.
I guess we won't be able
to go out for a while.
Just take it easy at home, okay?
Yeah...
Next in the news...
The annual fireworks display
will be held this weekend.
Fireworks show to be held this weekend
Many visitors from outside the city are
expected to come for the show.
Izumi-san?
Hey!
Huh?! What is it?
There's somewhere I'd like to go.
I'll go!
That was quick...
But your sunburn still hurts, right?
It'll be okay in a day or so.
You really are resilient.
So let's go see the fireworks.
Sure!
Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
Keep warm and go to bed early!!
Inuzuka-kun!!
Please Help
I'm going to an amusement park with
Shikimori-san next week. Suggestions...?
#06  With Fireworks Comes Summer's End
Free Entry
Ten Thousand
Bursts Reflect
in Your Eyes
as the Last
Lightning God
Dances Forth
from the Earth
19th
Annual
Fireworks Show
10,000 fireworks visible
from the main street!!
Lucky you, going to see the
fireworks with Mii-chan.
Is this a jinbei?
Hmm... Looks like my old one doesn't fit you.
Of course it doesn't.
He's nowhere near your size.
Go with a yukata.
Okay.
I haven't seen fireworks in ages.
They're so gorgeous,
but there's always such a big crowd.
Yeah, but apparently Shikimori-san has
never been to a live fireworks show.
Fireworks really are more impressive
in person, aren't they?
Yuu...
Yes?
There is something I must tell you.
Huh?
What is it?
How to Wear a Yukata: Women
Wind the ends of the datejime
sash around your back
and tie them in the front
Wind the ends of the
datejime sash around your back
and tie them in the front.
So this goes like this...
What the...
It's all tangled up!
I'll never get this done in time!
Lift up your arms.
O-Okay...
There. You're set.
Th-Thanks...
I swear, you're so clumsy.
What?
Suzumi Fireworks Show
Grand Venue
Takoyaki
Chocolate Bananas
Buttered Potatoes
Yakisoba
Waterproof smartphone case, check.
Bandages, check.
And I divided my money into three wallets,
so I can lose two and still be fine.
Okay!
No matter what happens to me today,
I'm gonna make sure Shikimori-san
enjoys the fireworks!
Mom, that guy is laughing to himself.
Shh!
That said, I hope I'll be able to find her...
Izumi-san!
Oh, good! Shikimori-san...
I hope I didn't keep you waiting.
Sh-She's so cute!
That yukata looks nice on you.
Y-Yours does, too, Shikimori-san.
You look amazing.
Th-Thank you.
Th-That yukata's really cute.
It has kind of a vintage feel.
It was my grandma's.
I've always wanted to wear it...
That's why I've really been looking
forward to today.
I see.
Well, shall we?
Yes.
Suzumi Fireworks Show
Grand Venue
Magic Show
Fireworks Show Stage
C O T T O N   C A N D Y
Here you go. One cotton candy.
Wow! It looks tasty!
Are you sure you don't
want one, Shikimori-san?
Yes, I'm fine.
Since I caused so much trouble
for you at the river,
I wanted to do something to thank you today.
You didn't cause any trouble for me.
But...
You always do so much for me,
and I can never do anything in return.
Well, the truth is...
I've never cared much for sweet things.
I had no idea.
Wait...
Those pancakes...
I could eat these every day.
Wait...
But recently, I've started
to warm up to them.
It must be because I always see a certain
someone enjoying them so much.
If you want to thank me,
you've done more than enough already.
But...
I think this might be a little too sweet.
Sh-She's just too cute...
Okonomiyaki
Draft Beer
Chocolate
Bananas
Cotton
Candy
Shaved Ice
Crêpes
Why don't we check out the other stalls?
S-Sure.
Oh, Shikimori-san!
Let's try the shooting game!
I'll get whichever prize you want.
Huh? The prize I want?
Which one do I want...?
Hey, that dog's pretty cute, isn't it?
Is that... a dog?
WOLF
Okay, I'll take that.
Better show your girlfriend
what you can do, bro!
Okay...
UTTER
FAILURE
T-Too bad, bro...
But here! You can have this kitty
on the house! Cheer up, okay?
Maybe I'll try my hand, too.
Oh? Think you can do it, little lady?
Go for it, Shikimori-san!
This game might be a little
too hard for a girl.
Why don't I give you one free shot?
There.
Who is she? This is no ordinary girl!
She definitely had the eyes
of a hunter just now!
That was amazing, Shikimori-san!
You're so cool!
That really touched me.
Here, little lady. It's all yours.
Thank you very much!
Here, Izumi-san.
Huh?
But you won it, Shikimori-san.
It's okay.
I won it for you, Izumi.
Ohmigosh...
Have a good time, you two!
How much are you gonna eat?
You can't have my chocolate banana.
I don't even want any sweet stuff.
Izumi!
Inuzuka-kun.
You're all here?
Yep. You guys came, too?
Get anything to eat?
I had cotton candy.
Ugh, sugar rush...
Micchon, your yukata's so cute!
Your hair looks nice, too.
Uh-huh! Braids with a yukata is super cute!
You both look cute in your yukatas, too!
Wearing one really lifts your spirits, huh?
Yeah, they're great!
Let's take a picture together!
Oh, good idea.
Check it out! We look super cute!
They're sure having a good time.
Let's take another one!
Well, since we all met up,
Let's get a full-body shot this time.
let's go try goldfish scooping!
Come on, Micchon! Scoot this way!
Sure.
It's on!
What is?
Well, it's no fun if we don't
make it a real contest!
That goes for everything!
Y-Yeah, I guess so...
Goldfish Scooping
Okay, here I go!
S-Sure.
Hup! C'mere!
How'd this happen?
Inu has a competitive streak a mile long.
Gotcha!
Heck yeah! My first catch!
Okay, my turn!
I knew this would happen!
Yeah, baby! I win!
I will avenge Izumi-san.
Challenge accepted.
Gotcha!
Shikimori-san's having trouble.
She might not be so hot at stuff
that requires this kinda dexterity.
Oh, here we go!
Hup!
Micchon, you're way too competitive.
This isn't good. The fireworks
are gonna start without us.
She's forgotten why she came here.
Leave this to me!
Huh?
The fireworks are about to start.
All right! It's on now, Inu!
Don't drop the "zuka"!
I'm gonna win this!
Th-Thanks!
Well, I'm not losing!
Forget about it. Just go.
Aw, man! Mine broke!
It's a bit of a walk from here. Is that okay?
Your feet don't hurt, do they?
No, they're just fine.
Where are we going?
Well, actually...
I want to take you somewhere.
Okonomiyaki
Draft Beer
Chocolate
Bananas
Cotton
Candy
Shaved Ice
Crêpes
Attention, attendees.
Suzumi Fireworks Show
Grand Venue
Please ensure that you have
all your personal belongings.
I managed to fix the strap, but...
You already have blisters, Shikimori-san!
I-I'm sorry.
Those have gotta hurt...
All that walking must have
been really painful.
You probably shouldn't do any more.
So, um...
Where did you want to take me?
Oh, nowhere important.
Please tell me!
W-Well, actually...
Dad told me about a little-known
spot to watch the fireworks.
Yuu...
Yes?
There is something I must tell you.
Wh-What is it?
There's a great viewing spot that
not many people know about.
R-Right.
It won't be crowded and it will have
a lovely view of the fireworks.
What? How do you know about it?
The two of us went there a long time ago.
You know a place like that?!
I want to go!
But your feet...
I can still fight!
Against what?! The pain?!
Don't talk like some kind of warrior!
Anyway, I'm not going to let
you walk any further,
so let's head to the usual spot.
All right. I guess we don't have a choice.
We can always come again next year, right?
Yeah. You're right.
Okay...
Here.
What are you doing?
I'll carry you on my back.
You can't walk, right?
No, no, no! I'm too heavy!
I'll snap you right in half!
I'll be fine. Let me help you out for once.
Uh... O-Okay, here I come.
Whoops... Whoa...
C-Careful!
Okay!
Let's go!
U-Um, I'm not too heavy, am I?
You're not pushing yourself?
I'm just fine!
Hold on tight.
How pretty...
The fireworks have started.
Huh? Izumi-san...
The fireworks aren't this way.
Are you lost?!
Sorry, Shikimori-san.
I still want to go to that secret spot!
W-With me on your back?!
Yep!
I'll walk!
Let me down!
Whoa, don't flail around.
You're hurting my arms.
Thanks.
You don't have to push yourself so hard...
I might not look it,
but I'm actually pretty strong.
We're climbing up there?
Yep.
But...
It's okay.
Why would you go through all this?
It's simple.
I want you...
to really, truly smile from the heart.
Oh, there it is!
We're almost there!
Keep it up, Izumi-san!
Whoa! Don't make me wobble!
We're here!
This is incredible, Izumi-san! Thank you!
You're welcome.
Anyway, there's no one here at all.
It really is a secret.
Oh, Izumi-san, there's a bench.
Yeah. Let's sit there.
Are you all right?
Yep! Totally fine.
This takoyaki is good!
So good. Too good.
Right?!
Wanna go buy some more?
Let's conquer all of the food stalls!
Hey, you're all pumped up, huh, Hachimitsu?
Well, shall we?
Hey! Watch the fireworks!
Shikimori-san, are your feet okay?
Oh... Yes, they're fine.
And, um... I apologize.
Huh?
For putting you through all that.
You don't have to worry about that. Really.
I know, but...
I guess knowing that and doing it
are two different things.
I just... want you to think I'm cute.
I don't want you to see me as weird or bad.
That line was the cutest of all!
But isn't it a little late for that?
I've already seen you doing
some pretty silly things,
and you get evil looks on
your face all the time.
Huh?!
You're kidding...
You're always so proper and perfect.
I think you could at least relax a little
in front of me without being embarrassed.
Always wanting to look good
is typical you, though.
Actually... I'm just like you.
Huh?
I couldn't even invite you here last year
because I was so afraid you wouldn't
like me anymore if I did.
We're still just friends, so inviting her to
the fireworks would be too obvious, right?!
What if I scare her off?!
I had no idea...
So you didn't come to see
the fireworks last year?
No.
I just listened to them from home,
cursing myself for being such a coward.
Ow! What was that for?!
You know, last year...
I was waiting all along for you to call me.
Uh... Y-You were? I-I'm so sorry.
It doesn't matter anymore.
It's okay now.
After all...
Just look at how pretty
this year's fireworks are.
Thank you for bringing me here!
Yeah, you're right.
They're... really pretty.
Well, ready to go home?
Aren't you at your limit already?!
Nope, I'm fine!
Or not!
I knew it!
D-Dad?!
Watch your step, son. That was dangerous.
Th-Thanks, Dad.
And use a light, would you?
Motoko-san! What are you doing here?
Huh? We've been here this whole time.
Right behind you.
Hey, isn't that Yuu and Mii-chan?
Don't, dear. You mustn't meddle.
Aren't yukatas nice?
Maybe I should've worn one this
year, too. It's been so long.
Shall we go buy some next year?
I wonder if they'll have your size.
Y-You were, huh?
I see...
They didn't hear us, did they?
I'll drive you both home.
You must be exhausted.
It's late, anyway.
Dad...
What's wrong? Do your feet hurt?
Thanks for telling me about this place!
The fireworks were beautiful!
That's great.
More importantly, are you
sure you can carry us both?
Oh, he'll be fine.
When he was younger,
he could carry four people.
What?!
SEE YOU~